Hannah Hawker

57 Cleveland Street Stones Corner 4120 0468 313 994 hannah.hawker@hotmail.com

April 25, 2014

Manager

Fresh Events + People 31 Jeays Street, Bowen Hills Queensland, 4006

Dear Sir or Madam.

I am writing to inquire about possible openings at Fresh Events as a Food and Beverage Attendant. My professional experience, as well as my out going personality makes me an excellent candidate for this position. I am also studying a Bachelor of Arts in Applied Theatre at Griffith University, which I am to complete in 2017.

As you will see from the enclosed resume, I have more than 6 months of experience in the field of food handling and preparation. My resume shows that I have been consistently rewarded for hard work with increased responsibilities. These rewards are a direct result of my expertise in this area, my commitment to personal and professional excellence, and my excellent written and oral communication skills.

If you have questions, or if you want to schedule an interview, please contact me at 0468 313 995. I look forward to meeting you to further discuss employment opportunities with Fresh Events.

Sincerely,

Hannah Hawker

Hannah Hawker

57 Cleveland Street, Greenslopes 4120 0468313995

Email: hannah.hawker@hotmail.com

OBJECTIVES

To obtain part time employment to enable me to support myself & save for my University Degree course which I am due to start in February 2014.

EDUCATION

Tamborine Mountain College

Year 11

Tamborine Mountain High School

Completed years 8-10 and year 12, 2012

QUALIFICATIONS

Graduated High School with an OP14 Responsible Service of Alcohol Certificate Safe Drive Test Drive Certificate Student Council Representative 2012

WORK HISTORY

Receptionist - Computex Solutions, Mt Tamborine

September 2013 – January 2014

- ② Answering phones
- ① Office Administration duties
- ① Greeting customers, handling initial enquiries

Waitress - Talk of the Town, North Tamborine

April 2013 – September 2013

- Waiting Tables
- (f) Front of House
- ② Barista Duties
- Operating the cash register
- Serving Customers

Casual Shop Assistant - Switch Boutique

January 2013 – January 2014

- Cleaning
- Stocktaking
- ① Dressing mannequins and designing displays
- ② Restocking shelves
- ② Serving Customers
- ② Operating the cash register

Children's Entertainer & Shop Promoter - Flights of Fancy, Gallery Walk

January 2011 – January 2013

- (f) Face painting
- Story telling
- ① Meeting & greeting customers
- Promoting the store along Gallery Walk
- ② Entertaining at children's parties

Receptionist - First Choice Property Centre, Nth Tamborine

January 2011 – December 2012

- Meet & greet office visitors
- Compiling and printing brochures & property books
- Sorting & filing documents electronically and manually
- ① Entering data into specialized real estate software
- ② Answer the phone & email enquiries
- ① Typing letters & general administration duties

Shop Assistant - Divine Scents, Gallery Walk

September 2009 – January 2010

- ① Cleaning dusting shelves, sweeping floors
- ① Unpacking boxes
- ② Restocking Shelves
- ② Serving Customers
- ① Operating the Cash register.

Canteen Assistant - Tamborine Mountain Soccer Club

April 2010 – September 2010

- Cooking
- Cleaning
- Restocking shelves
- Making and serving tea and coffee
- ② Serving Customers

① Operating the cash register

Pool Assistant - Tamborine Mountain Pool

September 2007 – January 2008

- ① Operating canteen
- Making Tea/coffee
- ① Cleaning kitchen/bathrooms
- ② Serving Customers

WORK EXPERIENCE

Apple Tree Creek Hotel, Apple Tree Creek

- ****Description**** Bartending Duties
- Pouring beer/mixing drinks
- Waitressing

SKILLS

Customer Service

Preparation & cooking of food.

Making Coffee in a café environment

Theatre Skills & performing

Cleaning, dusting and unpacking

REFERENCES

Jessica Gough – Switch Boutique

Ph: 07 5545 0256

Marcella Brearly – Apple Tree Creek Hotel

Ph: 07 4126 1216

David Parker – Talk of the Town Restaurant & Bar

Ph: 0424 053 013